[{"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Piers"]}, "docId": "121023pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["WP", "PRP", "VBD", "JJ", "IN", "JJS", ",", "NNP", ",", "VBZ", "WRB", "JJ", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", ":", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "VBG", "IN", "NN", "VBZ", "IN", "VBG", "DT", "NNP", "NNS", "WDT", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "TO", "VB", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 37, "question": "Did you like what you heard from the two candidates?", "question_tokens": ["Did", "you", "like", "what", "you", "heard", "from", "the", "two", "candidates", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "IN", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "CD", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 38, "answer": "What I was struck by most, Piers, is how remarkable it was that you have -- you know, running for president is about convincing the American people that you can be trusted to do what you say you're going to do.", "answer_tokens": ["What", "I", "was", "struck", "by", "most", ",", "Piers", ",", "is", "how", "remarkable", "it", "was", "that", "you", "have", "--", "you", "know", ",", "running", "for", "president", "is", "about", "convincing", "the", "American", "people", "that", "you", "can", "be", "trusted", "to", "do", "what", "you", "say", "you", "'re", "going", "to", "do", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121023pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "NN", "TO", "VB", "RP", "DT", "NN", "TO", "VB", "IN", "DT", "RB", ",", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 51, "question": "So what's the difference?", "question_tokens": ["So", "what", "'s", "the", "difference", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "WP", "POS", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 52, "answer": "The president spent a lot of time working throughout the administration to figure out a way to deal with a very, very difficult issue.", "answer_tokens": ["The", "president", "spent", "a", "lot", "of", "time", "working", "throughout", "the", "administration", "to", "figure", "out", "a", "way", "to", "deal", "with", "a", "very", ",", "very", "difficult", "issue", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"DATE": ["last three and a half years"], "ORGANIZATION": ["Piers", "Governor Romney"], "LOCATION": ["Osama"]}, "docId": "121023pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "RB", "DT", "NN", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "CC", "JJ", "NNS", "WDT", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "CD", "CC", "DT", "NN", "NNS", ",", "CC", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "NNP", ",", "DT", "NN", ",", "DT", "CD", "NNS", "DT", "NNPS", "VBP", ",", "NNP", "NNP", "VBD", "RP", "RB", ",", "RB", ",", "RB", "RBR", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NNS", ",", "VBG", "NNP", "NN", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 67, "question": "There were details on various things but in terms of a strategy, I thought they were pretty similar, wasn't it?", "question_tokens": ["There", "were", "details", "on", "various", "things", "but", "in", "terms", "of", "a", "strategy", ",", "I", "thought", "they", "were", "pretty", "similar", ",", "was", "n't", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["EX", "VBD", "NNS", "IN", "JJ", "NNS", "CC", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "JJ", ",", "VBD", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 68, "answer": "Well, clearly the governor embraced the strong and decisive policies that the president over the last three and a half years, but if you follow, and I know you have, Piers, the campaign, the 20 debates the Republicans have, Governor Romney staked out far, far, far more conservative positions on a whole host of issues, including Osama bin Laden.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "clearly", "the", "governor", "embraced", "the", "strong", "and", "decisive", "policies", "that", "the", "president", "over", "the", "last", "three", "and", "a", "half", "years", ",", "but", "if", "you", "follow", ",", "and", "I", "know", "you", "have", ",", "Piers", ",", "the", "campaign", ",", "the", "20", "debates", "the", "Republicans", "have", ",", "Governor", "Romney", "staked", "out", "far", ",", "far", ",", "far", "more", "conservative", "positions", "on", "a", "whole", "host", "of", "issues", ",", "including", "Osama", "bin", "Laden", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121023pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 112, "question": "How are you?", "question_tokens": ["How", "are", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 113, "answer": "I'm doing well.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "'m", "doing", "well", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121023pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "WP", "PRP", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 144, "question": "Have the Republicans got a problem because of that op-ed piece that Mitt Romney wrote basically distancing himself from a bailout?", "question_tokens": ["Have", "the", "Republicans", "got", "a", "problem", "because", "of", "that", "op-ed", "piece", "that", "Mitt", "Romney", "wrote", "basically", "distancing", "himself", "from", "a", "bailout", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "DT", "NNPS", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "IN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "WDT", "NNP", "NNP", "VBD", "RB", "VBG", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 145, "answer": "It's important to remember what he said.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "'s", "important", "to", "remember", "what", "he", "said", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Mitt Romney"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121023pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", ",", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 170, "question": "But then if you were watching Letterman last night, Mr. Speaker -- were you?", "question_tokens": ["But", "then", "if", "you", "were", "watching", "Letterman", "last", "night", ",", "Mr.", "Speaker", "--", "were", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "NNP", "JJ", "NN", ",", "NNP", "NNP", ":", "VBD", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 171, "answer": "No, I wasn't, unfortunately.", "answer_tokens": ["No", ",", "I", "was", "n't", ",", "unfortunately", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Letterman", "Mr. Speaker"], "TIME": ["last night"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"DATE": ["summer"], "ORGANIZATION": ["Virgin Airlines"], "PERSON": ["Richard Branson"]}, "docId": "121023pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "RB", ",", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "NNPS", ",", "WP", "IN", "NN", "VBZ", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "WDT", "JJ", "NN", "VBZ", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "NNS", "IN", "IN", "JJ", "NN", ",", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 186, "question": "Do you take it at face value?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "take", "it", "at", "face", "value", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "IN", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 187, "answer": "Well, I was with Richard Branson recently, the head of Virgin Airlines, who in fact is building a system that next summer is going to take people up into near space, near orbit.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "was", "with", "Richard", "Branson", "recently", ",", "the", "head", "of", "Virgin", "Airlines", ",", "who", "in", "fact", "is", "building", "a", "system", "that", "next", "summer", "is", "going", "to", "take", "people", "up", "into", "near", "space", ",", "near", "orbit", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121023pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "JJ", "RB", ",", "PRP$", "NN", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 236, "question": "I mean, what are we going to do with them?", "question_tokens": ["I", "mean", ",", "what", "are", "we", "going", "to", "do", "with", "them", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 237, "answer": "Well, funny enough, my brother is a British army colonel.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "funny", "enough", ",", "my", "brother", "is", "a", "British", "army", "colonel", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121023pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 243, "question": "Never seen them used in action?", "question_tokens": ["Never", "seen", "them", "used", "in", "action", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "VBN", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 244, "answer": "No.", "answer_tokens": ["No", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121023pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "NN", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 283, "question": "What would the odds have been on that, a Republican candidate mentioning peace 12 times to a Democratic president, zero?", "question_tokens": ["What", "would", "the", "odds", "have", "been", "on", "that", ",", "a", "Republican", "candidate", "mentioning", "peace", "12", "times", "to", "a", "Democratic", "president", ",", "zero", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "MD", "DT", "NNS", "VBP", "VBN", "IN", "DT", ",", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "VBG", "NN", "CD", "NNS", "TO", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 284, "answer": "And he talked about education and he talked about the importance of gender equality.", "answer_tokens": ["And", "he", "talked", "about", "education", "and", "he", "talked", "about", "the", "importance", "of", "gender", "equality", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121023pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 293, "question": "Did he achieve that aim?", "question_tokens": ["Did", "he", "achieve", "that", "aim", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 294, "answer": "Yes, I think he did.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", ",", "I", "think", "he", "did", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Obama"], "PERCENT": ["70 percent"]}, "docId": "121023pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "IN", "NN", "IN", "NNP", ",", "PRP", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "NNP", "POS", "NN", "CC", "PRP", "RB", "VBZ", "CD", "NN", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "MD", "VB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 305, "question": "What is your -- what is your sense of what's really happening in the battleground areas in particular?", "question_tokens": ["What", "is", "your", "--", "what", "is", "your", "sense", "of", "what", "'s", "really", "happening", "in", "the", "battleground", "areas", "in", "particular", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP$", ":", "WP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "WP", "POS", "RB", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NNS", "IN", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 306, "answer": "Well, I mean, in defense of Ante, he -- I mean he says that it might go Romney's way but he still says 70 percent chance that Obama will be re-elect.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "mean", ",", "in", "defense", "of", "Ante", ",", "he", "--", "I", "mean", "he", "says", "that", "it", "might", "go", "Romney", "'s", "way", "but", "he", "still", "says", "70", "percent", "chance", "that", "Obama", "will", "be", "re-elect", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Ohio"]}, "docId": "121023pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "RB", "TO", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 315, "question": "What is your gut feeling for the battleground battle in particular?", "question_tokens": ["What", "is", "your", "gut", "feeling", "for", "the", "battleground", "battle", "in", "particular", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 316, "answer": "I think that it will come down to Ohio.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "that", "it", "will", "come", "down", "to", "Ohio", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121023pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 351, "question": "Am I right?", "question_tokens": ["Am", "I", "right", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 352, "answer": "No.", "answer_tokens": ["No", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Mitt Romney"]}, "docId": "121023pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "PRP", "WP", "DT", "JJ", "NNP", "NNP", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 365, "question": "Isn't he much less threatening?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "n't", "he", "much", "less", "threatening", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "RB", "JJR", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 366, "answer": "You keep asking me who the real Mitt Romney is.", "answer_tokens": ["You", "keep", "asking", "me", "who", "the", "real", "Mitt", "Romney", "is", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121023pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": [":", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "TO", "VB", "IN", "NN", "VBZ", "RB", "VBN", "TO", "VB", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 383, "question": "What about what Hillary Clinton said about Barack Obama?", "question_tokens": ["What", "about", "what", "Hillary", "Clinton", "said", "about", "Barack", "Obama", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "IN", "WP", "NNP", "NNP", "VBD", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 384, "answer": "-- very different argument to say that someone is not qualified to hold office.", "answer_tokens": ["--", "very", "different", "argument", "to", "say", "that", "someone", "is", "not", "qualified", "to", "hold", "office", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Hillary Clinton", "Barack Obama"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Barack Obama"]}, "docId": "121023pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["VBG", "NNS", ":", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "IN", "PRP$", "NNS", ",", "VBZ", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 417, "question": "Who is my candidate?", "question_tokens": ["Who", "is", "my", "candidate", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 418, "answer": "Raising taxes -- wait, I assume your candidate, from your columns, is Barack Obama.", "answer_tokens": ["Raising", "taxes", "--", "wait", ",", "I", "assume", "your", "candidate", ",", "from", "your", "columns", ",", "is", "Barack", "Obama", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121023pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBG", ":"], "qSentId": 421, "question": "Are you not an Obama supporter?", "question_tokens": ["Are", "you", "not", "an", "Obama", "supporter", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "DT", "NNP", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 422, "answer": "I am saying --", "answer_tokens": ["I", "am", "saying", "--"], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Obama"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121023pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "qSentId": 424, "question": "You want to go ahead, Bissinger, or you want to let me finish?", "question_tokens": ["You", "want", "to", "go", "ahead", ",", "Bissinger", ",", "or", "you", "want", "to", "let", "me", "finish", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "RB", ",", "NNP", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 425, "answer": "Yeah.", "answer_tokens": ["Yeah", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Bissinger"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121023pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", "JJ", "NNS", "VBG", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NNS", ":"], "qSentId": 456, "question": "And if you don't, has he really earned the right to be re-elected?", "question_tokens": ["And", "if", "you", "do", "n't", ",", "has", "he", "really", "earned", "the", "right", "to", "be", "re-elected", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", ",", "VBZ", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "TO", "VB", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 457, "answer": "I absolutely hear people saying that they are proud of the things --", "answer_tokens": ["I", "absolutely", "hear", "people", "saying", "that", "they", "are", "proud", "of", "the", "things", "--"], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121023pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "JJ", ",", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 460, "question": "Do you believe he's done a great job in totality?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "believe", "he", "'s", "done", "a", "great", "job", "in", "totality", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 461, "answer": "I think on the whole, yes.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "on", "the", "whole", ",", "yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Charles"]}, "docId": "121023pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", ":", "CC", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "WP", "NNP", ":", "WP", "PRP$", "NN", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 472, "question": "What have you sensed in yourself about the choices in front of you that made you do that?", "question_tokens": ["What", "have", "you", "sensed", "in", "yourself", "about", "the", "choices", "in", "front", "of", "you", "that", "made", "you", "do", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBN", "IN", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "IN", "VBN", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 473, "answer": "Well, I mean, the reason I did it -- and it's a personal choice, and I respect what Charles -- what his decision is.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "mean", ",", "the", "reason", "I", "did", "it", "--", "and", "it", "'s", "a", "personal", "choice", ",", "and", "I", "respect", "what", "Charles", "--", "what", "his", "decision", "is", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121023pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "DT", "NN", "POS", "NN", "TO", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 537, "question": "What do you think of that, General Clark?", "question_tokens": ["What", "do", "you", "think", "of", "that", ",", "General", "Clark", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", ",", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 538, "answer": "I think it reflects the fact the country's gone to a volunteer force.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "it", "reflects", "the", "fact", "the", "country", "'s", "gone", "to", "a", "volunteer", "force", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Clark"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["France"]}, "docId": "121023pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "NNS", "IN", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 545, "question": "Why?", "question_tokens": ["Why", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "."], "aSentId": 546, "answer": "You know, we had a million men in France.", "answer_tokens": ["You", "know", ",", "we", "had", "a", "million", "men", "in", "France", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121023pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "PRP", "RB", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBD", "RB", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "IN", "CC", "VB", "NNS", "IN", "WP", "VBN", "RP", "TO", "VB", "RB", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 559, "question": "How important was it from your eyes?", "question_tokens": ["How", "important", "was", "it", "from", "your", "eyes", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "VBD", "PRP", "IN", "PRP$", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 560, "answer": "Well, I think to a great extent, it still leaves a lot of people concerned that the administration felt so necessary to get out and make pronouncements about what turned out to be false facts on the ground.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "think", "to", "a", "great", "extent", ",", "it", "still", "leaves", "a", "lot", "of", "people", "concerned", "that", "the", "administration", "felt", "so", "necessary", "to", "get", "out", "and", "make", "pronouncements", "about", "what", "turned", "out", "to", "be", "false", "facts", "on", "the", "ground", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121023pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 564, "question": "Were you pleased by what you heard from him?", "question_tokens": ["Were", "you", "pleased", "by", "what", "you", "heard", "from", "him", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 565, "answer": "I think it was a strategic move.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "it", "was", "a", "strategic", "move", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Great Britain"]}, "docId": "121023pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "RB", "MD", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 585, "question": "Do you think that's a fair assessment, that Obama, for all his critics, has in four years done a very different kind of style?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "think", "that", "'s", "a", "fair", "assessment", ",", "that", "Obama", ",", "for", "all", "his", "critics", ",", "has", "in", "four", "years", "done", "a", "very", "different", "kind", "of", "style", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "POS", "DT", "NN", "NN", ",", "IN", "NNP", ",", "IN", "PDT", "PRP$", "NNS", ",", "VBZ", "IN", "CD", "NNS", "NN", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 586, "answer": "That certainly may be the perception in Great Britain.", "answer_tokens": ["That", "certainly", "may", "be", "the", "perception", "in", "Great", "Britain", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Obama"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121023pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 598, "question": "Or is the answer that we need less going forward?", "question_tokens": ["Or", "is", "the", "answer", "that", "we", "need", "less", "going", "forward", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "JJR", "VBG", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 599, "answer": "We need a winning strategy.", "answer_tokens": ["We", "need", "a", "winning", "strategy", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}]